/*
   Thursday, June 1, 20236:50:38 PM
   User: 
   Server: Hi
   Database: sql
   Application: 
*/

'SINHVIEN' table saved successfully
'PHONG' table saved successfully
'KHOA' table saved successfully
'QUANLY' table
- Unable to create relationship 'FK_QUANLY_PHONG'.  
The ALTER TABLE statement conflicted with the FOREIGN KEY constraint "FK_QUANLY_PHONG". The conflict occurred in database "sql", table "dbo.PHONG", column 'maphong'.

